Guide to the E. S. Reddy Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Anti-Apartheid Conferences
  - Global Preparatory Meeting of Parliamentarians Against Apartheid, New Delhi, 1987 August 17-18 (Box 17, Folder 707 - 708)
  - Hague Roundtable on International Legal Issues Relating to Apartheid, Racism, and Racial Discrimination, 1985 September 4-6 (Box 17, Folder 709)
  - Hemispheric Seminar on Women Under Apartheid, Montreal, 1980 May 9-11 (Box 18, Folder 710)
  - International Atomic Energy Agency General Conference, 29thSession, 1985 September 26 (Box 18, Folder 711)
  - International Conference: 40 Years of the Nuremberg Process, Nuremberg, 1985 November 23-24 (Box 18, Folder 712)
  - International Conference Against Apartheid Sport, Zimbabwe, 1987 November 5-7 (Box 18, Folder 713)
  - International Conference in Solidarity with the Front Line States of Southern Africa, Lisbon, 1983 March 25-27 (Box 18, Folder 714)
  - International Conference in Solidarity with the Struggle of the Namibian People for Independence, Paris, 1983 April 25-29 (Box 18, Folder 715)
  - International Conference in Support of the Peoples of the Portuguese Colonies and Southern Africa, Khartoum, 1969 January 18-20 (Box 18, Folder 716)
  - International Conference in Support of the Struggle of the Namibian People for Independence, 1983 April 25-29 (Box 18, Folder 717)
  - International Conference of Experts for the Support of Victims of Colonialism and Apartheid in Southern Africa, Oslo, 1973 June 9-14 (Box 18, Folder 718)
  - International Conference of the German Association of Africanists, Hanover, Federal Republic of Germany, 1984 June 13-16 (Box 18, Folder 719)
  - International Conference of Trade Union Against Apartheid, Geneva, 1973 June 15-16 (Box 18, Folder 720)
  - International Conference of Trade Union on Sanctions and Other Actions Against the Apartheid Regime in South Africa, Geneva, 1983 June 10-11 (Box 18, Folder 721)
  - International Conference on Human Rights, Teheran, 1968 April-May (Box 18, Folder 722)
  - International Conference on Media Coverage of the African Continent, 1991 July 17-19 (Box 18, Folder 723)
  - International Conference on "Namibia and Human Rights," Dakar, 1976 January 5-8 (Box 18, Folder 724)
  - International Conference on Sanctions Against Apartheid Sport, London, 1983 June 27-29 (Box 18, Folder 725)
  - International Conference on Sanctions Against South Africa, Paris, 1981 May 20-27 (Box 18, Folder 726 - 727)
  - International Conference on South West Africa, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 728)
  - International Conference on the Alliance between South Africa and Israel, Vienna, 1983 July 11-13 (Box 18, Folder 729)
  - International Conference on Women and Apartheid, Brussels, 1982 May 17-19 (Box 18, Folder 730)
  - International Convention on the Suppression and Punishment of the Crime of Apartheid, 1981 January 12 (Box 18, Folder 731)
  - International Hearing on South African Aggression Against the Neighboring States, Oslo, 1983 March 22-24 (Box 18, Folder 732 - 733)
  - International Labor Conference, Geneva
    - 66thSession, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 734)
    - 68thSession, 1982 June (Box 18, Folder 735)
    - 72ndSession, 1986 June (Box 18, Folder 736)
  - International Labor Conference, 1988 June (Box 18, Folder 737)
  - International Meeting of Solidarity with Angola and Seminar on South Africa's Militarization, Brussels, 1975 October 17-19 (Box 18, Folder 738)
  - International NGO Action Conference for Sanctions Against South Africa, Geneva, 1980 June-July (Box 18, Folder 739)
  - International NGO Conference Against Apartheid and Colonialism in Africa, Geneva, 1974 September 2-5 (Box 18, Folder 740)
  - International NGO Conference for Action Against Apartheid, Geneva, 1978 August 28-31 (Box 18, Folder 741)
  - International NGO Conference for the Independence of Namibia and the Eradication of Apartheid, Geneva, 1984 July 2-5 (Box 18, Folder 742)
  - International NGO Conference of Action Against Apartheid and Racism, Geneva, 1983 July 5-8 (Box 18, Folder 743)
  - International Sanctions Workshop, Jos, Nigeria, 1983 December 7-11 (Box 18, Folder 744)
  - International Seminar on an Oil Embargo Against South Africa, Amsterdam, 1980 March 16 (Box 18, Folder 745)
  - International Seminar on Apartheid, Racial Discrimination and Colonialism in Southern Africa, U.N., Kitwe, 1967 July-August (Box 18, Folder 746)
  - International Seminar on Children, Paris, 1979 September (Box 18, Folder 747)
  - International Seminar on Eradication of Apartheid and Liberation of Namibia, Ghana, 1987 June 24-26 (Box 18, Folder 748)
  - International Seminar on Publicity and Role of Mass Media in the International Mobilization Against Apartheid, Berlin, GDR, 1981 August-September (Box 18, Folder 749)
  - International Seminar on Refugee Problems in Southern and Central Africa, Uppsala, 1966 April 26-28 (Box 18, Folder 750)
  - International Seminar on the Eradication of Apartheid and in Support of the Struggle for Liberation in South Africa, Havana, 1976 May 24-28 (Box 19, Folder 751 - 753)
  - International Seminar on the History of Resistance Against Occupation, Oppression, and Apartheid in South Africa, Paris, 1982 March-April (Box 19, Folder 754)
  - International Seminar on the Implementation and Reinforcement of the Arms Embargo Against South Africa, London, 1981 April 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 755)
  - International Seminar on the Legal Status of the Apartheid Regime in South Africa and Other Legal Aspects of Struggle Against Apartheid, Lagos, 1984 August 13-16 (Box 19, Folder 756)
  - International Seminar on the Role of Transnational Corporations in South Africa, London, 1979 November 2-4 (Box 19, Folder 757)
  - International Seminar on UN Arms Embargo Against South Africa, London, 1986 May 28-30 (Box 19, Folder 758)
  - International Seminar on Women and Apartheid, Helsinki, 1980 May 19-21 (Box 19, Folder 759)
  - International Student Conference in Solidarity with the Struggle of the Students of Southern Africa, London, 1987 July-August (Box 19, Folder 760)
  - International Symposium on "Strategies in the Struggle Against Apartheid," Stockholm, 1979 March 12-13 (Box 19, Folder 761)
  - International Youth and Student Conference of Solidarity with the Peoples, Youth and Students of Southern Africa, Paris, 1979 February 19-23 (Box 19, Folder 762)
  - International Youth and Student Seminar on "Youth Solidarity with the Peoples Struggle in Southern Africa", Geneva, undated (Box 19, Folder 763)
  - International Youth Conference Against Apartheid, New Delhi, 1987 January 8-9 (Box 19, Folder 764)
  - ISMUN 27thGeneral Conference, Sigtuna, Sweden, 1989 August 8 (Box 19, Folder 765)
  - Joint Seminar of the United Nations Association and (British) Anti-Apartheid Movement of Front Line State of Southern Africa, London, 1984 February 29 (Box 19, Folder 766)
  - Konferenz Südliches Afrika '84, Bonn, 1984 October 12-14 (Box 19, Folder 767)
  - Kongres gegen atomare Zusammenarbeit Bundesrepublik -Sudafrika, Bonn, 1978 November 11-12 (Box 19, Folder 768)
  - Latin American Regional Conference for Action Against Apartheid, Caracas, 1983 September (Box 19, Folder 769)
  - Lawyers Conference, Harare, 1989 February 4 (Box 19, Folder 770)
  - Luanda Nonaligned Ministerial Conference, Luanda, Angola, 1985 September 1-2 (Box 19, Folder 771)
  - Meeting of Jurists (organized by the Association of Soviet Lawyers and the International Association of Democratic Lawyers for International Anti-Apartheid Year), [1978 March 21, 1979 March 21] (Box 19, Folder 772)
  - Ministerial Meeting of the Coordinating Bureau of the Non-Aligned Countries, 1982 May - June (Box 19, Folder 773)
  - National Anti-Imperialist Conference in Solidarity with African Liberation, Illinois, 1973 October 19-21 (Box 19, Folder 774)
  - National Black Political Convention, Washington D.C., 1972 March 24 (Box 19, Folder 775)
  - National Conference for Sanctions Against Apartheid and Solidarity with the Liberation Struggle in Southern Africa, Stockholm, 1982 November 12-13 (Box 19, Folder 776)
  - National Conference in Support of the African National Congress and other Democratic Forces for a New South Africa, New York, 1992 November 13-15 (Box 19, Folder 777)
  - No Folder, undated (Box 19, Folder 778)
  - National Conference of South African Council Churches, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 779)
  - National Student Conference on South Africa and Namibia, New York, 1985 November 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 780)
  - NGO Symposium on World Peace and the Liberation of South Africa and Namibia, Geneva, 1986 June 11-13 (Box 19, Folder 781)
  - North American Regional Conference for Action Against Apartheid, New York, 1984 June 18-21 (Box 19, Folder 782)
  - NUS/AAM Conference on Southern Africa, Birmingham, 1973 June 6-8 (Box 19, Folder 783)
  - "Organization of African Unity at Twenty Five," New Delhi, 1988 September 6 (Box 19, Folder 784)
  - "Organizing Against Apartheid: The Labor Movement in South Africa", 1983 March 24 (Box 19, Folder 785)
  - Pan African Conference on Refugee, Arusha, 1979 May 7-17 (Box 19, Folder 786)
  - "Peoples of the World Against Apartheid for a Democratic South Africa," Arusha, 1987 December 1-4 (Box 19, Folder 787)
  - Public Hearing on the Activities of Transnational Corporations in South Africa and Namibia, New York, 1985 September 16-20 (Box 19, Folder 788)
  - Second Biennial Conference of the South African Council on Sport, Durban, 1977 October 8 (Box 19, Folder 789)
  - Second Brussels International Conference on Namibia, Brussels, 1986 May 5-7 (Box 19, Folder 790)
  - Second Conference of the Independent African States, 1960 June 14-24 (Box 19, Folder 791)
  - Second Conference of the International Trade Union Committee for Solidarity with the Workers and People of South Africa, Ghana, 1964 March 9-11 (Box 19, Folder 792)
  - Second Consultative Conference of the Pan Africanist Congress of Azania, Arusha, Tanzania, 1978 June-July (Box 19, Folder 793)
  - Second International Conference of Trade Unions Against Apartheid, Geneva, 1977 June 10-11 (Box 19, Folder 794)
  - World Meteorological Organization (Organisation Météorologique Mondiale), 1966 September 5 (Box 19, Folder 795)
  - Seminar on African Boundary Problems, Uppsala, 1968 May 7-10 (Box 19, Folder 796)
  - Seminar on Asian Youth and Student Actions Against Apartheid in South Africa, Hong Kong, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 797)
  - Seminar on Racist Ideologies and Organizations Hindering Efforts to Eliminate Apartheid, UN Special Committee Against Apartheid, Budapest, 1985 September 9-11 (Box 19, Folder 798)
  - Seminar on the Legal Aspects of Apartheid, Washington D. C., 1985 July 6-7 (Box 19, Folder 799-800)
    - Additional material (Box 20, Folder 801)
  - Seminar on the Military Situation in and Relating to Namibia, Vienna, 1982 June 8-11 (Box 20, Folder 802)
  - Seminar on the Role of the Latin American and Caribbean Media in the International Campaign Against Apartheid, Lima, 1988 March 7-9 (Box 20, Folder 803)
  - Seventh Conference of Heads of State or Government of Non-Aligned Countries, New Delhi, 1983 March (Box 20, Folder 804)
  - Socialist International Conference on Southern Africa, Arusha, Tanzania, 1984 September 4-5 (Box 20, Folder 805)
  - "Southern Africa: The Time to Choose," Conference, London, 1982 March 11-12 (Box 20, Folder 806)
  - Southern African Development Coordination Conference (SADCC): opening session, Lusaka, Zambia, 1984 February 2 (Box 20, Folder 807)
  - Special Meeting on Assistance to Mozambique, New York, 1989 April 14 (Box 20, Folder 808)
  - Special Seminar on the Caribbean and Africa, Jamaica, no year, May 22-25 (Box 20, Folder 809)
  - Summit Conference of Black Religious Leaders on Apartheid, New York, 1979 April 17-19 (Box 20, Folder 810)
  - Swedish Peoples' Parliament Against Apartheid, Stockholm, 1986 February 21-23 (Box 20, Folder 811)
  - Symposium on Current Issues Facing American Corporations in South Africa, New York, 1981 September 28 (Box 20, Folder 812)
  - Symposium on Strategies in the Struggle Against Apartheid, Stockholm, 1979 March 13 (Box 20, Folder 813)
  - Third Conference of Non-Aligned Countries, Lusaka, 1970 September 8-10 (Box 20, Folder 814)
  - Thirtieth Meeting of the Sub-Committee on Racism, Racial Discrimination, Apartheid and Decolonization of the Geneva NGO Sub-Committee on Human Rights, Geneva, 1979 March 13 (Box 20, Folder 815)
  - Twenty-First OAU Summit Conference, Addis Ababa, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 816)
  - Twenty-Second Conference of the South African Indian Congress, Johannesburg, 1956 October 21 (Box 20, Folder 817)
  - UN/OAU International Conference on Sanctions Against South Africa, Paris, 1981 May 20-27 (Box 20, Folder 818)
  - UNA/AAM Seminar on the Front Line States, 1984 February 29 (Box 20, Folder 819)
  - United Nations Human Rights Seminar on Apartheid, Brazil, 1966 August-September (Box 20, Folder 820)
  - United Nations Maputo Conference for Zimbabwe and Namibia, Maputo, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 821)
  - United Nations Media Roundtable on International Issues Relating to Apartheid, Racism and Racial Discrimination, The Hague, 1985 September (Box 20, Folder 822)
  - United Nations Seminar on Nuclear Collaboration with South Africa, London, 1979 February 24-25 (Box 20, Folder 823)
  - United Nations Seminar on the Legal Status of the Apartheid Regime and other Legal Aspects of the Struggle Against Apartheid, Lagos, 1984 August 13-16 (Box 20, Folder 824)
  - United Nations Seminar on the Role of Transnational Corporations in South Africa and Namibia, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 825)
  - United Nations Symposium on "Transnational Corporations in South Africa and Namibia," London, 1980 November 6-7 (Box 20, Folder 826)
  - No Folder, undated (Box 20, Folder 827)
  - U. S. Catholic Conference on Namibia, 1983 March 23 (Box 20, Folder 828)
  - Workshop on Southern Africa and Sanctions Against South Africa and Occupied Namibia, Sigtuna, Sweden, 1987 November 19-22 (Box 20, Folder 829)
  - World Conference Against Apartheid, Racism and Colonization in Southern Africa, London, 1978 March 22-23 (Box 20, Folder 830)
  - World Conference for Action Against Apartheid, Lagos, 1977 August 22-26 (Box 20, Folder 831 - 834)
  - World Conference on Sanctions Against Racist South Africa, Paris, 1986 June 16-20 (Box 20, Folder 835)
  - World Conference to Combat Racism and Racial Discrimination, Geneva, 1978 August 14-25 (Box 20, Folder 836)
  - World Health Organization Conference, Brazzaville, Congo, 1981 November 16-20 (Box 20, Folder 837)
- Namibia
  - Africa Fund, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 838)
  - American Committee on Africa, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 839)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement (Britain), undated (Box 21, Folder 840)
  - Canberra Conference on Namibia, Canberra, 1985 August 30-September 1 (Box 21, Folder 841)
  - Cape Democrats, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 842)
  - "A Century of Heroic Struggle of the Namibian People Against Colonial Occupation," New York, 1984 October 31 (Box 21, Folder 843)
  - "Children in Occupied Namibia," London, 1988 October 29 (Box 21, Folder 844)
  - Commission on Independence for Namibia, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 845)
  - Commonwealth Secretariat, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 846)
  - Conference on the Intensification of Internal Action for the Independence of Namibia, New York, 1985 September 11-13 (Box 21, Folder 847)
  - Emergency Conference on Namibia, New York, 1981 March 13 (Box 21, Folder 848)
  - English Language Programme for Namibians, Lusaka, 1983 October 19-27 (Box 21, Folder 849)
  - Episcopal Church People for a Free Southern Africa, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 850)
  - International Association of Democratic Lawyers (Belgium), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 851)
  - International Conference in Solidarity with the Struggle of the People of Namibia, Paris, 1980 September 11-13 (Box 21, Folder 852)
  - International Conference in Support of the Struggle of the Namibian People for Independence, Paris, 1983 April 25-29 (Box 21, Folder 853)
  - International Defence and Aid Fund (IDAF), 1976-1989 (Box 21, Folder 854)
  - Irish Anti-Apartheid Movement (Dublin), 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 855)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights, 1984-1990 (Box 21, Folder 856)
  - Lutheran World Federation, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 857)
  - Namibia Association, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 858)
  - Namibia Communication Centre (London), 1986-1990 (Box 21, Folder 859)
  - Namibia Support Committee (London), 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 860)
  - National Namibia Concerns, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 861)
  - National Union of Namibian Workers (NUNW), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 862)
  - Northeast Southern Africa Solidarity Network (NESASN), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 863)
  - Organization of African Unity (OAU), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 864)
  - Personal Notes on Namibia, undated (Box 21, Folder 865)
  - Second Brussels International Conference on Namibia, Brussels, 1986 May 5-7 (Box 21, Folder 866 - 867)
  - South West Africa People's Organization(SWAPO), 1965-1980 (Box 21, Folder 868)
    - Additional material, 1981-1990 (Box 22, Folder 869-870)
    - Pamphlets, undated (Box 22, Folder 871)
  - Sweden, 1981-1987 (Box 22, Folder 872)
  - Transnational Corporations, 1982-1989 (Box 22, Folder 873)
  - Tripoli Declaration, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 874)
  - United Nations, 1969-1991 (Box 22, Folder 875-876)
  - United Nations General Assembly, 1979-1983 (Box 22, Folder 877-878)
  - United Nations International Conference in Support of the Peoples of Zimbabwe and Namibia (Maputo), 1977 May 16-21 (Box 22, Folder 879)
  - United Nations Resolutions on Namibia, 1966-1990 (Box 22, Folder 880-882)
  - Uranium, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 883)
  - Washington Office on Africa, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 884)
  - World Peace Council, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 885)
  - World University Service, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 886)
- Missions to the United Nations
  - African National Congress (ANC) Observer Mission at the United Nations, 1980-1993 (Box 23, Folder 887-888)
  - Angola, 1974-1990 (Box 23, Folder 889)
  - Argentina, 1969-1981 (Box 23, Folder 890)
  - Australia, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 891)
  - Barbados, 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 892)
  - Belgium, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 893)
  - Botswana, 1977-1991 (Box 23, Folder 894)
  - Canada, 1977-1990 (Box 23, Folder 895)
  - Costa Rica, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 896)
  - Cuba, 1975-1984 (Box 23, Folder 897)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 898)
  - Denmark, 1969-1985 (Box 23, Folder 899)
  - Egypt, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 900)
  - Ethiopia, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 901)
  - Federal Republic of Germany, 1976-1989 (Box 23, Folder 902)
  - Finland, 1968-1982 (Box 23, Folder 903)
  - France, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 904)
  - German Democratic Republic, 1974-1989 (Box 23, Folder 905)
  - Ghana, 1974-1989 (Box 23, Folder 906)
  - Greece, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 907)
  - Iceland, 1977-1984 (Box 23, Folder 908)
  - India, 1982-1990 (Box 23, Folder 909)
  - Iran, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 910)
  - Ireland, 1974-1984 (Box 23, Folder 911)
  - Israel, 1977-1984 (Box 23, Folder 912)
  - Jamaica, 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 913)
  - Japan, 1983-1989 (Box 23, Folder 914)
  - League of Arab States, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 915)
  - Lesotho, 1970-1993 (Box 23, Folder 916)
  - Libyan Arab Republic, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 917)
  - Malaysia, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 918)
  - Mexico, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 919)
  - Netherlands, 1980-1984 (Box 23, Folder 920)
  - New Zealand, 1974-1991 (Box 23, Folder 921)
  - Nigeria, 1963-1992 (Box 23, Folder 922)
  - Norway, 1970-1989 (Box 23, Folder 923)
  - Organization of the Islamic State (Observer Mission), 1990 (Box 23, Folder 924)
  - Pakistan, 1975-1979 (Box 23, Folder 925)
  - Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO), 1983 (Box 23, Folder 926)
  - Pan Africanist Congress (PAC)- Observer Mission, 1977-1992 (Box 23, Folder 927)
  - People's Republic of Bulgaria, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 928)
  - People's Republic of China, 1982-1991 (Box 23, Folder 929)
  - People's Republic of Mozambique, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 930)
  - Philippines, 1974-1979 (Box 23, Folder 931)
  - Republic of Korea, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 932)
  - Republic of Namibia, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 933)
  - Republic of Sierra Leone, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 934)
  - Republic of Zimbabwe, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 935)
  - Seychelles, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 936)
  - Singapore, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 937)
  - Socialist Federal Republic of Yugoslavia, 1982-1990 (Box 23, Folder 938)
  - Socialist Republic of Vietnam, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 939)
  - Somalia, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 940)
  - South Africa, 1966-1980 (Box 23, Folder 941-943)
    - Additional material, 1982-1993 (Box 24, Folder 944-956)
  - Sri Lanka, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 957)
  - Sudan, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 958)
  - Swaziland, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 959)
  - Sweden, 1965-1991 (Box 24, Folder 960)
  - Tanzania, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 961)
  - Togo, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 962)
  - Uganda, 1975-1990 (Box 24, Folder 963)
  - Ukrainian SSR, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 964)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1977-1990 (Box 24, Folder 965)
  - United Kingdom, 1965-1989 (Box 24, Folder 966)
  - United Republic of Tanzania, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 967)
  - United States of America, 1966-1990 (Box 24, Folder 968)
  - Venezuela, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 969)
  - Zambia, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 970)
- Writings and speeches of E. S. Reddy, 1963-1991 (Box 25, Folder 971-979)
  - Indian South Africans in Struggle for National Liberation, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 980 - 981)
  - Struggle for Liberation in South Africa and International Solidarity, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 982 - 984)
  - Additional writings and speeches, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 985-986)
- Research material
  - Gandhi correspondence with South Africa, 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 987)
  - Indian South Affairs, 1906-1948 (Box 26, Folder 988-991)
- United Nations
  - Special Committee Against Apartheid, 1963-1977 (Box 27, Folder 992-1006)
    - Additional material, 1978-1992 (Box 28, Folder 1007 - 1021)
  - Center Against Apartheid, 1963-1972 (Box 28, Folder 1022-1025)
    - 1973-1981 (Box 29, Folder 1026 - 1038)
    - 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 1039 - 1046)
    - 1985-1992 (Box 31, Folder 1047 - 1057)
  - Press releases, 1963-1979 (Box 32, Folder 1058-1073)
    - 1979-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1074 - 1089)
    - 1986-1993 (Box 34, Folder 1090 - 1097)
  - Economic and Social Council, 1966-1983 (Box 35, Folder 1098-1105)
    - Additional material, 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 1106 - 1108)
  - Security Council: General, 1963-1982 (Box 37, Folder 1109-1125)
    - Additional material, 1983-1992 (Box 38, Folder 1126 - 1138)
  - Security Council: Limited, 1963-1988 (Box 39, Folder 1139 - 1164)
  - Resolutions and decisions, 1986-1991 (Box 40, Folder 1165 - 1170)
  - Namibia, 1966-1982 (Box 41, Folder 1171-1183)
    - Additional material, 1983-1988 (Box 42, Folder 1184 - 1195)
  - Food and Agricultural Organization (FAO) of the United Nations, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 1196)
  - General Assembly, 1980-1990 (Box 43, Folder 1197)
  - International Atomic Energy Agency, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 1198)
  - International Labor Office, 1983-1985 (Box 43, Folder 1199)
  - Secretariat News, 1988-1990 (Box 43, Folder 1200)
  - Security Council Official Records, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 1201)
  - United Nations Center for Human Settlements, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1202)
  - United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF), 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1203)
  - United Nations Department of Public Information, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 1204)
  - United Nations Educational and Training Program for Southern Africa (UNETPSA), 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1205)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1979-1993 (Box 43, Folder 1206)
  - United Nations Institute for Training and Research (UNITAR), 1980-1993 (Box 43, Folder 1207)
  - United Nations Non-Governmental Liaison Service, undated (Box 43, Folder 1208)